Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. General Subject files
  - Subseries 3. Colorado River
    - Sub-subseries 3. Boulder Canyon Project
      - Annuities Necessary to Make Replacements to Properties to be Operated, Maintained and Replaced by the United States - 10/21/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Estimated Replacement Annuity Required for Power Plant Structure and Generating Equipment Operated by Bureau of Power and Light at Boulder Power Plant - 10/21/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Suggested Basis of Allocation of Generating Charges to the States and Special Contractors for Metropolitan Power - 12/20/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Contract for Operation of Boulder Power Plant - the United States of America and the City of Los Angeles and its Department of Water and Power and the Southern California Edison Co., Ltd. - draft of - draft of 11/14/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - TS memorandum, n.d., W. L Chadwick to G. E. Trowbridge re: copies of exhibits to Mr. Ely, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Contracts: USA and Southern California Edison Co., Ltd.; USA and Metropolitan Water District of Southern California; USA and the City of Pasadena; USA and the State of Nevada; USA and the City of Burbank; USA and the City of Glendale; USA and the Nevada-California Electric Corporation; USA and the Defense Plant Corporation; USA and the California-Pacific Utilities Corporation; USA and the Citizens' Utilities Co., Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Memorandum of agreement between the U. S. Bureau of Mines and the U.S. Bureau of Rec~1Jmation covering lease of land for construction and operation of mineral beneficiating and recovery plants and the furnishings of supplies of electrical energy and water for the use in the operation thereof, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Drafts of Energy Contracts - 1941, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Contract for Resale of Electrical Energy - USA and the Citizens' Utilities Co., Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Contract for the Delivery of Water, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Contract for Resale of Energy - USA and the Defense Plant Corp., Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Administrative Problems in the Preliminary Phase of the Planning - and Construction of the Hoover Dam, by William James Bruce, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Appendix - draft of 5/27/43 revised 10/11/43 and 10/12-13/43 contract for delivery of water, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Statement of California's Boulder'Power.Contractors with respect to the Report of Expenditures from Colorado River Dam Fund Incurred in the Construction, Operation and Maintenance of, Boulder City, filed by the Secretary of the Interior pursuant to the powers contained in the Interior Department Appropriation Act for the fiscal year ending 6/30/44 (57 Stat. 451), Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Contract for the resale of electrical energy to be developed at Boulder Dam Power Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Report on Expenditure from the Colorado River Dam Fund Incurred in the construction, Operation and Maintenance of Boulder City, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Contract for the Resale of Electrical Energy at Boulder'Dam Power Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Contract Providing for Use of Certain Generating Equipment at Boulder Power Plant, Apportionment of Charges Therefor and Other Matters, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Reprint from Con~ssional Record - The Name of Hoover Dam, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Contracts for resale of Electrical Energy - copy for Northcutt Ely, Accession no. M0223 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - "The Threat" - article by Lee, 5/17/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Excerpts from the Legislative History of the Boulder Canyon Project Act re: the Power of the Secretary of the Interior to allocate water, Accession no. M0223 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Congressional Record - 7/2/35 - pgs 10623, 10624, Accession no. M0223 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous notes, Accession no. M0223 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Sub-subseries 4. Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act
      - Legislative History of the adjustment act - Congressional'Record, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Report on Competitive Value of Falling Water for Primary Energy At Boulder Canyon in Competition with Steam Power at the Load Center in Southern California, by A. B. Roberts, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Memorandum Presented by the Proposed Operating Agents Regarding Extent to Which Determinations of the Secretary are to be Subject to Review in Arbitration or Court Proceedings, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - In the Matter of Procedure Under the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - Brief Statement of the Principal Questions to be Determined - Submitted in behalf of the City of Los Angeles and its Department of Water and Power and the Southern California Edison Co., Ltd., Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Statement Prepared for the Convenience of and the Use by Arizona's Representatives at the Oral Hearings to be Held on December 17, 1934, Before the Secretary of the Interior, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Boulder Dam Legislation on an "Amortization Basis" Instead of a "Competitive Rate" Basis, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes - first draft, 12/2/37, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes - draft of 12/7/37, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes - draft of 1/27/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Report for the Upper Colorado River Basin Committee on the Engineering and Financial Analysis of Proposed Boulder Canyon Pro- -ject Adjustment Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes - draft of 2/11/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - draft of 3/4/39, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Statement Concerning Propriety of and Basis of Payments to the States of Nevada and Arizona Provided Under the Boulder Canyon Project Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Boulder Canyon Project -- summary of financial operation, 5/22/39, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - information sheet lle Reasons for Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - TL photocopy, 5/17/39, W. F. Durand to E F. Scattergood re: rise in price of fuel oil in Los Angeles, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Interest Rate in the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Statement Concerning the Proposed Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act Submitted Jointly on Behalf of the Sates of the Colorado 'River Basin and the Boulder Dam Power Allottees, 4/15/39, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Alternative for Section 6 - Interest Rate and Authority to Issue Refunding Bonds, 3/26/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Stock market quotations, 3/21/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - The Proposed Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - Information, 4/15/39, with Explanatory Introduction and Authorizing Resolution, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - Agency Contracts, 1940, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Proposed Boulder Canyon Project Act - Information, 6/4/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Agency Contract Exhibits, 8/12-15/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Tentative and Partial Draft Proposed by Department of Water and Power of the City of Los Angeles with Order Promulgating- Rates and Basis of Charges Under the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act,ll/27/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Statement on Behalf of Southern California Edison Co., Ltd.',, re: leasehold rights at Boulder Canyon, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Draft of Proposed Findings and Recommendations for the Effectuation of the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act, Washington, D.C., 2/19/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Wright's Findings and Determinations in the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act, 2/7/41 - 3/14/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Reply to Wright, 3/14/41, with drafts of 3/6, 3/8, 3/11, 3/12, 3/13, 3/14, Accession no. M0223 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - TL mimeographed, 4/7/41, E. F. Scattergood to Secretary of the Interior, Accession no. M0223 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Statement of Aubrey N. Irwin, City Attorney of the City of Glendale, California Before the Hon. Harold L. Ickes, Secretary of the Interior, Washington, D.C., 4/8/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Agency Contract and folder of material for N. Ely, 4/22/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Contracts and Regulations Pursuant to the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act Between the United States of America and the City of Los Angeles and its Department of Water and Power,5/29/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Boulder Canyon project - black binder with information of the regulations for the sale of power, Accession no. M0223 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - TLS, 7/1/41, M. Schmitz (sec. to Mr. Robinson) to N. Ely re: enclosing copies of several project documents, etc., Accession no. M0223 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Short form - Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Long form - Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act., Accession no. M0223 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Outline of agency contract, Accession no. M0223 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Contracts under the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - folder of information on various aspects, Accession no. M0223 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 5124 - Binder with notes, legislative history, amendments, letters, information, Accession no. M0223 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Material on Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act - folder, Accession no. M0223 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Annual Reports of Operations under the Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - List of materials transmitted re: Boulder Canyon Project Adjustment Act and predecessor bills, Accession no. M0223 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Sub-subseries 5. Colorado Water Users' Association
      - Minutes of the 19th Meeting, Colorado River Commission, 11/19/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Minutes of the 20th Meeting, Colorado River Commission, ll/19/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Minutes of the 21st Meeting, Colorado River Commission, ll/20/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Minutes of the 22nd Meeting, Colorado River Commission, ll/22/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Minutes of the 23rd Meeting, Colorado River Commission, ll/22/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Minutes of the 24th Meeting, Colorado River Commission, ll/23/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Minutes of the 25th Meeting, Colorado River Commission, l1/23/22, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Minutes of the27th Meeting, Colorado River Commission, Accession no. M0223; ll/24/22 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Minutes of the Conference of the States of the Colorado River' Basin at Santa Fe, 3/17-18/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Transcript of Proceedings of the Meeting of the Colorado River Basin States at Phoenix, Arizona, 6/22-23/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Proceedings of the Committee of the 7 States of the Colorado River Basin, El Paso, Texas, 6/17-20/42, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Dowd's Interstate Conference notes, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Proceedings of the 2nd Annual Conference of the Colorado River Water User's Association, Salt Lake City., Utah, 2/11-13/46, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Proceedings of the 9th Annual Conference of the Colorado River Water Users' Association, Las Vegas, Nevada, 12/8-9/52, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Minutes of the Meeting of the Colorado River Users' Association, Las Vegas, Nevada, 5/1-2/47, Accession no. M0223 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Sub-subseries 6. Colorado River Storage Project
      - Legislative History of the Colorado River Storage Project Act, Vol. 1, 83rd Congress, 1953 - 1954, Accession no. M0223; 1 binder (Box 69)
      - Legislative History of the Colorado River Storage Project Act, Vol. 2, 84th Congress, 1954 - 1955, Accession no. M0223; 1 binder (Box 70)
      - North of Lee Ferry, Vols. 1 - 3, by John U. Terrell, Accession no. M0223 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Engineering and Economic Analyses of Colorado River Storage Project and Participating Projects Proposed by U. S. Bureau of Reclamation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Brief Summary of Protective Provisions of Colorado River Storage Project Act, P. L. 485, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Statement of Chet Holifield, M.C., on H.R. 3383, the Colorado River Storage Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River Storage Project and Participating Projects - Introduction, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Statement of Colorado River Board of California, 6/2/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - From the Office of U. S. Senator Thomas Kuchel, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Statements on H.R. 4449 and S.1555, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Memorandum on H.R. 4449 and S. 1555 - Colorado River Storage Project, 1954, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Another Big Bill to the Nation's Taxpayers for the Colorado River Storage Project, House Bill H.R. 4449 - a Report from 9 Congressmen - What Each State will Pay, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Colorado River Storage Project, 1954 - Colorado River Board Computations, Tabulations, misc. notes, Accession no. M0223 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Colorado River Storage Project, 1954 - Basic Documents, Comments, Notes - Testimony for California, Questions to the Depts. of the Interior and Budget, Proposed Amendments to H.R. 4449 Committee Reports, Senators' Statements, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Echo Park - an Unprecedented Invasion of the National Park System, by Rep. John P. Saybor 6/8/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Cost to Nation's Taxpayers by State of the Colorado River Storage Project and the Fryingpan-Arkansas Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - The Colorado River Storage Project 6/20/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Congressional Record Reprint: Statement of John F. Kennedy on the Upper Colorado River Basin, 8/20/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River Board of California Technical Committee Meeting10/14/57, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Congressional Record Reprint: Extension of Remarks by John P. Sayer - Hidden Subsidies, 5/3/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Hydrologic Bases for Financial Studies - Colorado River Storage Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Congressional Record Reprint: Extension of Remarks by John P. Sayer - Upper Colorado River Storage Project and Participating Projects, 4/7/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Opening Remarks of Assistant Secretary of the Interior Fred G. Aandahl at Conference with the Governors and Other Representatives of the States of the Colorado River Basin10/24/57, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Congressional Record Reprint: Statment of Thomas H. Kuchel - The Colorado River Storage Project and Participating Projects, 8/2/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Colorado River Storage Project, Binder #1, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Tearsheet - Newsweek, 4/12/54 - Perspectives by Raymond Moley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Legislative History of the Colorado River Storage'Project Act Relating to the Navajo Irrigation Project and San Juan-Chama Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Tearsheet - Newsweek, 5/9/55, Perspectives by Raymond Moley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Colorado River Storage Project - Graphs and Charts, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Tearsheet - Newsweek, 5/10/54, Perspectives by Raymond Moley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Electric Utility Transmission System Study as Related to the Colorado River Storage Project 10/1/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Tearsheet - Newsweek, 5/17/54, Perspectives by Raymond Moley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Legislative History, Sec. 7, 9, 14 and 15 - the Colorado River Storage Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Tearsheet - Congressional Record, 7/7/55, pg. 8639, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Repayment Analyses - the Colorado River Storage Project 5/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Statement of Northcutt Ely Before House Interior and Insular Affairs on H.R. 270, 84th Congress, to Authorize Construction of the Colorado River Storage Project, 3/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Colorado River Storage Project, 1955, Analyses, Computations, etc., Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Colorado River Storage Project Bills, H.R. 270, 2836, 3383, 3384, 4488, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Witnesses before the House Hearings on Colorado River Storage Project, 3/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Senate Presentation, 3/3-4/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Senate Hearings - Colorado River Storage Project S. 50, 3/3/55 - Statements of Matthew, Morris, Ely, Hewes, Griffith, Howard, Tillman, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - House Hearings - Colorado River Storage Project H.R. 270, 3/17/55, Statements of Simpson, Hewes, Ely, Tillman, Griffith, Morris, Matthew, Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Accession no. M0223 (Box 68, Folder 1244491555)
    - Sub-subseries 7. Colorado Compact
      - Pact Criticism is Largely on What It does not Say, Accession no. M0223 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Colorado River Compact, Accession no. M0223 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - H.J. Res. #2, Accession no. M0223 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Arizona's Rights in the Colorado River - Proposals of Arizona and the Counter-Proposals of California Submitted to the Tri-State Conference now in Progress by Sen. A. H. Favour, 8/16/29, Accession no. M0223 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Statement by Gov. R. C. Stanford (Arizona) at Boulder Dam Power Conference, 4/16/37, Accession no. M0223; (2 copies) (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - misc. notes, Accession no. M0223 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Analysis of the Provisions of the Colorado River Compact, by Gilbert F. Nelson, Accession no. M0223 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries 8. Glen Canyon
      - Legal Memos re: Glen Canyon Criterion, Accession no. M0223 (Box 74)
      - Glen Canyon Project Act Amendment, 10/3/51, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Material submitted to Schroen from which compilation was mimeographed, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Proposal agreed upon 10/21/57 - approved by governors, 10/22/57, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Arizona's proposal submitted 10/22/57 as an alternative to California's proposal to delete 2nd sentence of paragraph II of the 3 states' draft (#2a), Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - California's counter-proposal submitted 10/21/57 after consideration of Arizona's proposal, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Arizona proposal submitted 10/21/57, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - California's counter-proposal, submitted 10/21/57 after consideration of Arizona's proposal (#2d), Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Representatives' meeting, October 21, 1957, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Same as #2, mimeographed, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Department of Interior release, 10/9/57, Meeting Called on Glen Canyon Reservoir, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - TL mimeo, 4/26/57, N. Ely to Fred W. Simpson re: Glen Canyon Dam and Power Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Excerpt from transcript of meeting on Glen Canyon Reservoir held in the Interior Department Auditorium, 10/24/57, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Glen Canyon Criterion, Vol. 1, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Glen Canyon Criterion, Vol. 2, Accession no. M0223 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Meeting on Glen Canyon, 10/24/57, Accession no. M0223 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Summary - Glen Canyon Filling Studies, by Lower Basin Engineering Group, 3/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - The Future Operation of Glen Canyon Reservoir as Related to the Colorado River Compact - A Study for the Colorado Water Conservation Board by the Colorado Water Investigation Commission,7/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Status Report, Glen Canyon Filling Studies Prepared by the Engineering Group Representing Arizona, Nevada, California and the Bureau of Reclamation, 3/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Sub-subseries 9. Lower Basin Compact
      - California Proposals for a Lower Basin Compact, 3/7/29, Accession no. M0223 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Proposals to a basis for a Lower Basin Compact, 3/3/29, Accession no. M0223 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Boulder Canyon-Lower Colorado River Power and Water Set Up, 1/1/28, Accession no. M0223 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda and letters re: Lower Colorado River Basin Compact, Accession no. M0223 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Report of Proceedings - Hearings held before the Commission on Interior and Insular Affairs, H.R. 4671, To Authorize the Construction, Operation and Maintenance of the Lower Colorado River Basin Project and for Other Purposes, 7/27/66, Accession no. M0223 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Report of Proceedings - Hearings held before the Commission on Interior and Insular Affairs, H.R. 4671, To Authorize the Construction, Operation and Maintenance of the Lower Colorado River Basin Project and for Other Purposes, 7/28/66, Accession no. M0223 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Sub-subseries 10. Mexican Water Treaty
      - Colorado River International Problem, by the Colorado River Commission of Arizona, 6/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - The International Boundary Commission - United States and Mexico, by Charles A. Timm, 9/8/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - A Statement of the 6 States Committee (Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, Texas, Utah and Wyoming) Supporting Ratification of the Proposed Treaty Between the United States and Mexico with Respect to the Water of the Colorado River, Tijuana River and Rio Grande, 8/9/44, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 3)